dbsbank.in 2015-10-23

# regulatory

**This policy applies to DBS Bank Limited (“DBS”) in India.**

**Clear and easily accessible Statements of Practices and Policies**

As a part of DBS’s ongoing efforts to ensure the compliance of modern banking approach, customer trust/ satisfaction, security oriented service and banking services, DBS has adopted the privacy policy aimed at protecting the personal information entrusted and disclosed by the customer (the "Policy"). This Policy governs the way in which DBS collects, uses, discloses, stores, secures and disposes of personal information.

The Policy is in compliance with the Information Technology (Reasonable security practices and procedures and sensitive personal data or information) Rules 2011 (the “ **IT Rules** ”) contained in the Information Technology Act 2000.

**Purpose of Collection and Use of Personal Information  ** 

DBS collects and uses the financial information and other personal information from its customers. This information is collected and used for specific business purposes or for other related purposes designated by DBS or for a lawful purpose to comply with the applicable laws and regulations. DBS shall not divulge any personal information collected from the customer, for cross selling or any other purposes.

The authenticity of the personal information provided by the customer shall not be the responsibility of DBS.

Any information that is freely available or accessible in public domain or furnished under the Right to Information Act, 2005 or any other law for the time being in force shall not be regarded as personal information for the purposes of this Policy and DBS shall not be responsible for the same.

**Disclosure of Personal Information**

The personal information collected by DBS shall not be disclosed to any other organization except:

  1. where the disclosure has been agreed in a written contract or otherwise between DBS and the customer;
  2. where the disclosure has been agreed in a written contract or otherwise between DBS and the customer;
  3. where DBS is required to disclose the personal information to a third party on a need-to-know basis, provided that in such case DBS shall inform such third party of the confidential nature of the personal information and shall keep the same standards of information/ data security as that of DBS.

**Reasonable Security Practices and Procedures**

DBS shall take reasonable steps and measures to protect the security of the customer’s personal information from misuse and loss, unauthorised access, modification or disclosure. DBS maintains its security systems to ensure that the personal information of the customer is appropriately protected.

DBS ensures that its employees respect the confidentiality of any personal information held by DBS.

**Amendments**

DBS reserves the right to change or update this Policy or practice, at any time with reasonable notice to customers on DBS web site so that customers are always aware of the information which is collected, for what purpose DBS uses it, and under what circumstances, if any, DBS may disclose it.

**Response to Enquiries and Complaints**

DBS encourages customer enquiries, feedback and complaints which will help us identify and improve the services provided to our customers. Please contact us on our Helpline - 18002094555 / 18001039897 or write to us at [www.dbs.com/in](http://www.dbs.com/in).
